http://www.686.com/pages/privacy-policy

PRIVACY STATEMENT
This privacy statement contains our information, explains personal data and the processing of personal data and for what purposes we process your personal information. It explains your rights, what we do to ensure your personal data are safe and how long they are stored. This privacy statement applies when you visit our website (https://www.686.com), place an order or close contracts.
Our information
Westlife Distribution, LLC 227 E. Compton Blvd Gardena, CA 90248 USA 310.818.2300 info@686.com www.686.com
Personal data
Personal data are data that provide information about you that directly or indirectly identify you.
Processing personal data
By processing personal data we mean the collection, recording, organization, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by forwarding, dissemination or otherwise making available, combining, blocking, erasure or destruction of your personal data.
Purposes
We process your personal data for the following purposes: so that we can contact you, for the ordering process, the implementation of the agreement, so that we can inform you of changes to our services or products, so that we can deliver our products or services to you, to send newsletters if you gave permission, for general or targeted offers, for your account on our website, to post reviews. We only process personal data that are necessary for these purposes.
We also process your personal information to fulfill legal obligations, improve our services, to investigate complaints and to prevent fraud. We never sell your personal information to third parties. We draw up profiles of you or take automated decisions that can have significant consequences for you. In order to take care of your personal data, we conclude a processing agreement with companies if those companies process your data in our assignment.
Personal data that we process
In order to carry out the purposes, we process the following personal data:
- First and last name
- Address
- Phone number
- E-mail address
- IP address
- Bank account number
You also have rights
Wish to know which personal data we processed? Send an email to info@686.com with a request for access to your data. You will receive a response to the request within four weeks.
Are your personal data incorrect, incomplete, irrelevant for the purposes for which they are processed or otherwise in breach of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) or other legislation? Then you have the right to correction of your personal data. Correction means correction, addition, deletion or blocking of your personal data. You also have the right to object to the processing of your personal data, the right to have less data processed, the right to withdraw permission you have given and the right to data portability. Send your request to info@686.com. Or contact us by phone: 310.818.2300. You will receive a response to the request within four weeks.
Safety
Personal data are personal and should remain personal. We find it just as important as you that your personal data do not go public or are processed unlawfully. We therefore apply all possible technical and organisational measures to safely handle your personal data. To secure your personal data we use security software such as a virus scanner and firewall, passwords for electronic systems, a secure internet connection and backups.
Storage personal data
We do not store your personal data longer than is strictly necessary for carrying out the purposes. If there are legal requirements applicable to the storage, the personal data are no longer stored than required by law.
CHILDREN'S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
COOKIE STATEMENT
The 686 website may use “cookies”. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your device that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information and improve your experience. We use cookies to help us remember and process the pages you have visited items in your shopping cart, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business only. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, most browsers allow you to enable or disable the cookie feature. Please refer to your browser’s help section for specific instructions on how to manage cookies. Because cookies are used throughout our websites, disabling them may prevent you from using certain parts of the site.
Overview cookies:
Functional necessary cookies
We place functional cookies to make our website work well. No permission is required for placing these cookies. This concerns cookies that make sure preferences are saved, information is remembered when you go to another subpage, logins are stored, it is remembered if you have given permission to post cookies, abuse can be detected, the load of the website is distributed, the shopping cart is working and data is remembered for the ordering process.
Social media cookies
To share content from our website on social media, Facebook, Twitter and Instagram will place cookies.
Tracking cookies
We continuously improve our website by analyzing how you use our website, how you found us and where there are any bottlenecks.  Cookies are placed by Google Analytics.
Ad cookies
To ensure you do not see the same ad every time, offers match your interests, we know how many visitors click on an ad and how many people eventually make a purchase cookies are placed by Google, Facebook and Twitter.
We do not store cookies longer than required by law and not longer than is strictly necessary for carrying out the purposes.
If other parties place cookies, their cookie statement applies. This may change in the meantime. The current cookie statement can be found on the website of the party concerned.
You can also delete cookies
Via your web browser (the program that allows you to view websites) you can delete cookies. How this should be done depends on the Internet browser. We have created a short guide for the most common Internet browsers.
Google Chrome: Go to Settings, click Advanced Settings, click Clear Browsing Data, select Cookies, and Other Site and Plug-in Details, and then click Clear Browsing Data.
Internet Explorer: Go to Settings, click Clear Browsing Data, select Cookies and Saved Website Data, and click Delete.
Safari: Go to Preferences, click Security, click Show Cookies, click Delete All, or select one or more cookies and click Delete.
Mozilla Firefox: Go to the menu and choose Options, select Privacy, choose use custom settings for History at Firefox, click on Show Cookies, click on Delete All Cookies, or select one or more cookies and click on Delete Selected.
Is your web browser not included? Or have the settings changed in the meantime? Then use the help or search function of your Internet browser.
Changes
We can change the information in this cookie statement without notice. Changes are required, for example, if we modify our website or if the legislation is modified. We encourage you to check regularly if the information provided and the text of this cookie statement have been changed.
